Alexandr Fadeev

CONTACTS

11 Rabochaya Street, Podolsk, Moscow region, Russia, 142116

Mobile: +7 (999) 920-45-25 Email: frogcatcher@mail.ru Telegram: @frogitcher

PROFILE

Individual with 3.5 years experience in Planning component for self-driving vehicles. Good knowledge of C++ programming language and classic algorithms and data structures. Experience with classic optimization.

Successful competitive programmer in past. Teacher and coach of various schools and bootcamps. Currently working on AI for Navio self-driving car.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present	Navio (ex. SberAutoTech) Software engineer
Speed planning for self-driving car:	Developed library of solvers for speed profile planning from ground up, using both discrete and continuous optimization. Implemented features for speed planning solvers. Supported components «around» speed planning.
Self-driving car planning:	Developed features for geometry planning solvers. Optimized existing geometry planning algorithms.
2021 - 2022	Yandex Self-Driving Group Software engineer
Automatic remote requests for unwanted situations prevention	Developed and implemented unwanted situations detectors. Supported transition from «Watcher» to «Resolver-only» methodology of robots overseering.
Robot routing	Developed features and fixed bugs for adaptation of self-driving car routing system for robot purposes.

2022 - Present

NUST MISIS Lecturer and seminarian

Done: $\frac{5 \text{ semester-long courses on Algorithms and Data Structures and C++}}{\text{programming language as a lecturer and/or a seminarian.}}$

ACM MISIS Coach Teaching and administating

Supervised several programming platform.

Done: Was a lecturer on several programming bootcamps.

Was a informatic teacher assistant in school №179 in Moscow.

FORMAL EDUCATION

2023 - Present NUST MISIS Postgraduate

Thesis topic: Speed planning for self-driving car

NUST MISIS Master's degree

2020 – 2023 Informatics and computer engineering

2016 – 2020 NUST MISIS Bachelor's degree

Applied mathematics

SUPPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

2017 - 2022 ACM MISIS Student Competitive programming

Solved algorithmic problems.

Done: Participated in one-man and three-man contests for 3 years.

Took part in programming bootcamps.

4-times ICPC semifinalist, 3-times prize winner.

Achieved: Prize winner of various programming contests.

Master rank on Codeforces programming platform.

Finalist of Russian AI Cup 2022 - CodeRoyale